bashbound.com 2017-06-26

# Privacy

(Last update: Oct 2013)

### Information we gather

The following information may be gathered from our website visitors:  
IP address and user agent (browser). We also collect and track additional anonymous user data. You may opt out of anonymous data tracking if you wish by clicking [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). More opt out information can be found [here](http://www.revmountain.com/optout.html).

### How we use the information we gather

We use the information to enhance your visitor experience and to keep track of our website activities, specially for internal analysis and tracking which may be used by third parties.

### The people that are given access to this information

Your personal information is accessible by the Dealeez.com administrator(s). We may also share your data with interested third parties.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, check out [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

### The security measures we have in place to protect your personal information

To safeguard your personal information, we keep all collected data at our secure database center.

### Our use of cookies

Our website makes use of cookies which are small digital files that are stored in your web browser that enable us to track your return visits to our website.

Your browser settings may allow you to block these cookies, but we recommend you have them enabled to help us personalise your experience of our website.

Additionally, 3rd party advertisers on our site may use cookies for tracking purposes.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors based on their visit to sites they visit on the Internet.

Website visitors may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We, or a data provider we have engaged, may place a unique cookie on your browser - cookies enable you to receive customized ads, content or services. We or our data providers may also read/recognize the cookies on your browser as well. The cookies may contain demographic data, or other data, linked to information that you voluntarily submitted to us, e.g., your email address.

**Short Message Service.** We may make available a service either directly or through third parties by which you can receive commercial text messages on your wireless device via short message service ("SMS Service"). Data obtained from you in connection with this SMS service may include your name, address, cell phone number, your provider's name, and the date, time, and content of your messages. Company may also obtain the date, time and content of your messages in the course of your use of the SMS Service. We will use the information we obtain in connection with our SMS Service in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If fees are charged to your wireless account invoice, we may provide your carrier with your applicable information in connection therewith. Your wireless carrier and other service providers may also collect data about your wireless device usage, and their practices are governed by their own policies. Company does not guarantee that your use of the SMS Service will be private or secure, and we are not liable to you for any lack of privacy or security you may experience. You are fully responsible for taking precautions and providing security measures best suited for your situation and intended use of the SMS Service. You may opt out of the SMS Service at any time by replying "STOP", "END", or "QUIT" to the SMS text message you have received.

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use your personal information in connection with our advertising, content, e-commerce, promotional and service programs and other business activities (the "Program") and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services and the sites of our advertisers.

**What Information We Collect**

When you visit our site we may collect two types of information: (a) personal information you actively choose to disclose and (b) information about you that is collected automatically by our servers or obtained from third parties in a way not visible to you.

(a) _Information you actively choose to provide._ By choosing to participate in our Program, you must become a Member by disclosing the following information, such as: your email address, name, address, phone number and birth date. During the process of registering on our site, participating in various offers, completing surveys, or sending us emails or correspondence, we collect additional information that you may disclose, including for example mobile telephone number, fax number, payment information (e.g., credit card number and billing address), credit information, social security number, health information and personal preferences regarding lifestyle, products or services.

(b) _Passive information collected automatically by our servers or obtained from third parties._ We collect some information about you simply by virtue of you connecting to our web site. Our servers automatically identify your computer and location by its internet protocol ("IP") address, a unique string of numbers that is assigned to your computer by your internet service provider. In addition, to participate in our program you must allow cookies to be active on your system. Cookies are a feature of web browser software (Internet Explorer, Netscape Navigator, etc.) that allows web servers to recognize which computer is used to access a web site. Cookies simplify subsequent interactions on our site and streamline your transactions on related web pages. Information collected through cookies may include the date and time of your visits, the site pages you viewed, the time spent at each page, and the web sites you visited just before and just after our site. You can disable the cookie function by following the instructions in the "help" section of your browser. However, doing so will likely make it impossible for our system to properly recognize you when you visit our sites, and consequently may make your participation in our program more difficult or impossible. In addition to the information you provide or that is collected automatically from our system, we may obtain information about you from our marketing partners or other third parties, and we combine that information with the information you actively provide or that is automatically collected by our servers.

The term "Information" is used in this policy to refer to both types of information described above, as well as any Information that you provide to us directly by phone (including any phone number displayed via caller ID), text or SMS message, U.S. mail or through any other written or oral communication with us.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may collect and use information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media, such as mobile apps, about goods and services that may be of interest to you, and to understand how users respond to advertising on our website and other websites. These companies may collect this information using technologies such as cookies and pixels. We may also share personal information such as your email address in hashed non-human readable form with these advertising companies. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, check out <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

**How We Use And Share The Information Collected**

We use your Information to administer our business activities, provide customer services such as technical support, distribute information about changes to our site, and send you, and enable others to send you, information about products and services that may be of interest to you and to contact you or use your Information for any other purpose. We send communications to you ourselves, and your Information also is shared with other organizations that may contact you for any purpose by email, phone, text message, U.S. mail or any other means of communication.

In addition to the information collected by us and registration information submitted by you, we may employ both first-party and third-party cookies. A cookie is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing activity-based information about you, and it is designed to facilitate the receipt of targeted and relevant advertisements. The cookie is not associated with your personally identifiable information.

One of our third-party cookie partners is Datran Media (for Datran Media?s privacy policy, please visit http://www.datranmedia.com/privacy/). To opt out of Datran Media?s cookie-based marketing program, click [here](http://rt.displaymarketplace.com/optout.html).

**OPT-IN NOTICE: By Participating, You Expressly "Opt In" To Receive Information And Grant Us Permission To Share Your Information**

By signing up for our Program you expressly opt in to receive future information about products and services from us and from a variety of advertisers to whom we may provide your Information. We will share your personal information with third parties, including but not limited to our advertisers, BigRewards.com, ShoppingBag.com and HotSurveys.com (collectively Media Network, Inc.) for any reason we choose, including without limitation for the following purposes: (1) to operate our Program (including the transfer of the information to advertisers or to third parties who maintain on our behalf a list of persons having registered with our Program), (2) to permit advertisers or other third parties to use your Information for any purpose such as contacting you by email, phone, text message, U.S. mail or any other means of communication for any purpose, (3) to confirm you have completed all of the necessary steps to receive your gift, and (4) as we are required to do by law, including to notify the IRS that you received your gift. As a result, we will transfer your Information to third parties whose privacy policies and practices are beyond our control.

In addition, in the event we consider a transaction involving the purchase or sale of our assets or stock, other companies may review our records, including your Information, to make business decisions about the transaction. Likewise, your Information may be transferred to third parties in the event of the sale or acquisition of our company or any of its assets. The parties who perform services for us (credit card processors, merchant banks, our internet service provider, etc.) also may have access to your information in performing their services.

**Special Note About Information You Provide Directly To Our Advertisers.**

You are able to access certain advertiser's sites through our site. When you opt to receive information or sign up for an offer from an advertiser, you may be doing so through third party sites and with other companies over which we have no control. You should read those sites' privacy policies to make sure you agree to them before using such sites. If you wish to opt out of those advertisers' mailings, you must do so directly with such advertisers or as otherwise provided on or through their sites.

**Third Party Ad Servers.**

We may serve advertisements within our Web Site either ourselves or by allowing other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to do so. In addition, some of our advertisers may use the services of third-party ad networks. Some of these third-party ad networks may place a persistent cookie on your computer. Doing this allows the third-party ad network to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, third-party ad networks may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows a third-party ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. We do not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third-party ad servers or third-party ad networks. Those third-party ad networks that use persistent cookies may offer you a way to opt-out of ad targeting. You may find more information at the web site of either the individual third-party ad network or the Network Advertising Initiative (http://www.networkadvertising.org), Privacy Choice (http://www.privacychoice.org/choose), and Digital Advertising Alliance (http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). 

**Security Of Your Information.**

We use reasonable technical efforts to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, or accidental loss or destruction of Information. However, nearly all Internet transmissions pass through many servers not controlled by us, and therefore we cannot guarantee that any information you provide us or we collect will not be intercepted or altered in that process. Also, as noted above, your Information is shared with third parties whose privacy policies and practices are beyond our control. 

**How You Can Choose To "Opt Out" Of Receiving Further Information About Products Or Services**

If at any time you do not wish to receive further information about products or services from us and wish us to cease providing your Information to third parties, you may choose to "opt-out" through the Unsubscribe/"Opt-Out" page of our site or by written request sent to our Customer Service Manager at the following email address:

Customer Service Department  

Opt Out Link  
Unsubscribe

Please note that we do not directly conduct email campaigns. Entry of your email in the unsubscribe link above will not stop email delivery from the publisher from which you received the original offer (i.e. you may still receive emails from this publisher, with offers other than our services). To opt out of receiving any email offers from the publisher, please follow the publisher's opt out instructions provided in the email. 

If you choose to proceed in the unsubscribe link above, your email will be compiled into a suppression file for future email campaigns for this offer. This suppression file list will be provided to all third parties providing email solicitations for our services. By entering your email, you authorize us to provide this aggregate list to those third parties for the purpose of removing your email address from the future of this offer via email. It may take up to 10 business days/ 2 weeks) to take effect, and we will do our best to ensure that all publishers sending this offer will remove your email address prior to deployment. 

We will promptly update our records upon receiving your clear instructions to opt-out, but it may take up to ten (10) business days from our receipt of your request for the change to be fully effective. If you later give us a clear statement that you want to receive emails from us or our advertisers after such date, then that opt-in statement will supersede any earlier opt-out request. If we have already provided your email address or other information to an advertiser or other third party before we receive your opt-out request, we cannot prevent them from sending or continuing to send you information or emails and you will need to contact such third party directly.

**How To Correct, Delete Or Access Your Information**

If you wish to access, delete or correct the information you have provided to us through this site, please contact us through the Contact Us section of our site or through written request sent by U.S. mail to the Customer Service Manager at the address listed above.

**Special Rights For Residents Of Certain States**

If you are a California resident or another state with specific laws relating to the collection and use of Information, you may have specific rights not set forth in this policy. For example, California residents have the right to receive: a) information identifying any third party company(ies) to whom we may have disclosed, within the past calendar year, personal information pertaining to you and your family for the company's direct marketing purposes; and b) a description of the categories of personal information disclosed. To obtain such information you must make a request in writing. Your request must include your name registration (email address), the site name you visited and a return address or it will not be processed. We will not honor such requests more than once per calendar year. Requests made via email will not be accepted. Please mail your request to Customer Service Manager at the address listed in the footer of this site or the Contact Us page.

PLEASE CHECK THIS PRIVACY POLICY PERIODICALLY FOR CHANGES AS WE RESERVE THE RIGHT TO REVISE THIS PRIVACY POLICY. SUCH REVISIONS TO THE PRIVACY POLICY SHALL TAKE EFFECT WHEN POSTED. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF OUR SERVICES THROUGH ANY COMMUNICATION CHANNEL FOLLOWING THE POSTING OF ANY CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY CONSTITUTES YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF SUCH CHANGES.
